In the season of storms
Two made it by one, easily
In the dawning sunset,
At night in the early afternoon, casually
No matter how bad our bodies decay
We'd love to laugh at the end of time
No matter what you're fighting for
I want you to be motivated by love
No need to look for brand-new days
They're always here with us
Though I've seen a lot of things in my life
My eyes will always & forever be sparkling
Though I've lived that life so long
Everything I've been thru is like a dream
Everything looks attractive
But you're the only one for me
Where have you been, I've been looking for you
Take me there, take me there
Giving up everything and going with you
To anywhere, To everywhere
In extreme weather, in a crazy crowd
With you I can go, smoothly smoothly
Our brand-new future, awkward past,
Everything will be shiny (Kirari)
Looking back on what I had to lose
...makes me weep
Sometimes I'm lost at sea
Just swaying in the wind, unsteadily
I came running out of breath
Already decided where to go
I'd rather not get lost but who knows
I thought I knew something
In fact I knew nothing
But now at least I know it and I'm so glad
No need to look for brand-new days
They're always here with us
here with us, with us, Ah
Though I've seen a lot of things in my life
My eyes will always & forever be sparkling
forever be sparkling,
Ah, though I've lived that long
Everything I've been through is like a dream
Everything looks attractive
But still you're the only one for me
Where have you been, I've been looking for you
Take me there, take me there
Giving up everything and going with you
To anywhere, To everywhere
In extreme weather, in a crazy crowd
With you I can go, smoothly smoothly
Our brand-new future,
Our awkward past,
Everything will be shiny (Kirari)